https://www.thunderstruckfilms.com/about-us/terms-and-conditions/

TERMS & CONDITIONS
Terms and Conditions:
Any information submitted stays strictly in-house at Thunderstruck Films. We promise not to sell or share the info with anyone else. All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used and protected by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this privacy policy. We maintain strict security over the info you give us and will only use it for the following reasons:
• To process your order.
• To send you information you have requested from Thunderstruck Films and to update you on the status of your information request.
• Send you free promotional materials.
• Use the information to monitor consumer browsing patterns and site usage to help us develop and design the layout of our website.
• To disclose personal information when we believe release is necessary to comply with the law, enforce or apply Terms & Conditions or protect the rights, property, or safety of Thunderstruck Films, our users, or others.
Cookies
Information is stored whenever you interact with us. We use cookies allowing specific information to be gathered when your web browser accesses our site. You can stop the use of cookies by changing the settings on your web browser.
Secure Checkout
Checkout from Thunderstruck Films is securely done through Paypal Inc. When redirected from our site.  This is where all payment information will happen for your purchase at Thunderstruck Films.
Electronically Speaking
By using our website and providing the information requested you agree that we may collect and use this information. When you visit Thunderstruck Films or send emails to us, you are communicating with us electronically and agreeing to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on this site. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so you are informed about what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Too Many Emails?
Updates will be sent to you via email giving you a heads up about special offers, new product releases, news, and events that might interest you regarding our company. If you do not wish to receive any further emails from us please email jim@thunderstruckfilms.com with your request along with the email account you would like removed from our database.
Kids Web Serving Policy
Kids Under the Age of 13 – We are committed to protecting the online privacy of children. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13.
Kids under the Age of 18 – Sorry dude’s, but if you are under 18, you may shop at thunderstruckfilms.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Don’t even think about stealing your mom’s credit card!
Shipping Terms:
Shipping will be processed through your Paypal Transaction when placing your order.  They will be shipped via USPS and if you have any questions please feel free to contact jim@thunderstruckfilms.com regarding questions about shipping.
Questions/Comments
Please direct any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy to: jim@thunderstruckfilms.com
